<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Scrolling Text2</string>
    <string name="article_title">The three body problem</string>
    <string name="article_subtitle">Remembrance of Earth\'s Past </string>
    <string name="article_text">This is the most impactful sci-fi series I\'ve ever read.
        What I mean by that, is that this series has permanently changed:
        the way I look at the stars, the way I perceive time,
        the way I think about life, the way I think about SETI,
        the way I think about the meaning of life,
        the way I think about human beings\' place in the universe, the way I view technology, etc.
        \n\n
        This series well and truly \"blew my mind away\".
        This isn\'t a page0-turning space opera adventure kind of story.
        The story is interesting and good, and there is most definitely some drama and entertainment - and the writing is excellent (translation to English is superb).
        But the main thing for me about this series is that it educated me about physics and really made me look at EVERYTHING through a new lens.
        The ideas in this book I had never encountered before - and I am a voracious reader.
        I found this series to be totally original and mind-blowing.
        There were time where I simply needed to put it down after reading only a short time, in order to simply ponder the ideas presented.
        I\'ve never had quite an experience like this with a book.
        \n\n
        Buy it on Amazon at https://www.amazon.com/Three-Body-Problem-Remembrance-Earths-Past-ebook/dp/B00IQO403K</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main2">Main2Activity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
