<resources>
    <string name="app_name">intentChallenge</string>
    <string name="mainText_hint">Press any of these buttons to read</string>
    <string name="text_button_one">Text One</string>
    <string name="text_button_two">Text Two</string>
    <string name="text_button_three">Text Three</string>
    <string name="first_para">This whitepaper is intended for existing and potential customers who are
designing the security infrastructure and configuration for applications running
in Amazon Web Services (AWS). It provides security best practices that will help
you define your Information Security Management System (ISMS) and build a set
of security policies and processes for your organization so you can protect your
data and assets in the AWS Cloud. The whitepaper also provides an overview of
different security topics such as identifying, categorizing and protecting your
assets on AWS, managing access to AWS resources using accounts, users and
groups and suggesting ways you can secure your data, your operating systems and
applications and overall infrastructure in the cloud.\n\n
The paper is targeted at IT decision makers and security personnel and assumes
that you are familiar with basic security concepts in the area of networking,
operating systems, data encryption, and operational controls.\n\nThe paper is targeted at IT decision makers and security personnel and assumes
that you are familiar with basic security concepts in the area of networking,
operating systems, data encryption, and operational controls.\n\nThe paper is targeted at IT decision makers and security personnel and assumes
that you are familiar with basic security concepts in the area of networking,
operating systems, data encryption, and operational controls.</string>
    <string name="second_para">Information security is of paramount importance to Amazon Web Services (AWS)
customers. Security is a core functional requirement that protects missioncritical
information from accidental or deliberate theft, leakage, integrity
compromise, and deletion.\n\n
Under the AWS shared responsibility model, AWS provides a global secure
infrastructure and foundation compute, storage, networking and database
services, as well as higher level services. AWS provides a range of security services
and features that AWS customers can use to secure their assets. AWS customers
are responsible for protecting the confidentiality, integrity, and availability of
their data in the cloud, and for meeting specific business requirements for
information protection. For more information on AWS’s security features, please
read Overview of Security Processes Whitepaper.</string>
    <string name="third_para">The IAM service is one component of the AWS secure global infrastructure that
we discuss in this paper. With IAM, you can centrally manage users, security
credentials such as passwords, access keys, and permissions policies that control
which AWS services and resources users can access.\n\n
When you sign up for AWS, you create an AWS account, for which you have a
user name (your email address) and a password. The user name and password let
you log into the AWS Management Console, where you can use a browser- based
interface to manage AWS resources. You can also create access keys (which
consist of an access key ID and secret access key) to use when you make
programmatic calls to AWS using the command line interface (CLI), the AWS
SDKs, or API calls.</string>
</resources>
